Hello friends, we will talk about 8 companies.
Next week from April 18 to 231 is going to be a
busy week. Quarterly
results have started coming. Eight
companies are coming with their results and
Eden will also release their results. In today's video, we will
discuss them. Let's start
with Mindtree. Their results are going to come on April 18
and
Mindtree is also going to declare dividend. The second
name is Angel One. Friends, their results
and final dividend will come on April 22. If we look at the last one year,
you can see Engine One's dividend as per the dividend pair.
In April 2022, they declared a dividend of Rs. 70,
then in January, a total of Rs.
10, they have declared a dividend of Rs. 10 in April 2022.
Then
in October, a
dividend of Rs. 5.70, then in July, a dividend of Rs. 5.15, a
total of Rs. 2455. It
seems that the dividend was declared like Engine One. The
next name is ICICI
Securities.  The
pay is important, the result is about to come, the final dividend
of AD Securities and Lemon
Juice Front Part Paisa is the interim dividend
by them and they had
declared it in the month of October, so we will
know what has been the final decision.
Disclosure friends, we have had a fight with Engine One and ICICI
Securities,
so these were the disclosures, I am
putting before you, the next thing is LIC,
Tata Elxsi, April 2015 result is about to come,
dividend declarers, dividend
result both will be fixed at ₹40,
in the last financial year there was a dividend of
Rs.24, here there was a special dividend of Rs.24, chair price
whenever you see, you will see around 8300 82 29,
then the next name is
HCL Tech, step by step, two big results have
already come, Infosys and TCS,
so such an attack that if you look in plastic wrap, then there is
a big name whose results are about to
come, so for a moment both the result and
dividend will come and
what is special about HCL Tech  1026 weakness curative
quarterly dividend was presented to them, so for the
last 19 years,
dividend has been coming from such tractor in every quarter and this
time already three quarters have passed
so total 226 its dividend by ₹10 ₹10 and
Rs.6 so total 26 its
dividend has been paid this time, it will be
interesting how much they pay at this time,
they have also
made a policy for the same, they took clarity
from the department regarding accident, whatever they earn till 2276, then
75% of it will be their dividend, so this is the
policy for a special dividend, the next
name is Tata Communications Tata Group, another
name Airplane 21-3-2018 both are coming,
in the last financial year dividend of ₹15,
see your share price is
around ₹100, Paytm Larsen
& Toubro Group company results are on 21st April
and  There is dividend also, you will see that
they have given a good return. If
you look at the last one and a half years, then
they have already given a dividend of Rs.20 in this financial year.
In the last financial year, the final dividend was made
₹10 paisa. This time it will increase or decrease.
You will know about this ATS.
Now the last name is ICICI Bank. Friends, we have to
wait for April 23. HDFC Bank
results have come. Strong results have come.
HDFC Bank has made a profit of more than Rs. 10,000 crore.
Now ICICI Bank is on top. The
Ghaghra is continuously increasing.
Both are
known for their profit. But this time, if you look at the
previous share dividend and ICICI Bank
and its share, you will see that right now
you will see it near 206. So, I
hope you have got value in this video.
Now we will also keep previewing some companies which are important
companies,
so do subscribe to the channel
so that accurate information
and knowledge keeps reaching you. Thank you for your time.  Thank
you